Guide to the 2000 Voting Technology Archive.
Voting Technology Archive, 2000
- Series VII: Audio Visual Material
  - Unprecedented: the 2000 Presidential Election, V930 (Box 19)
  - Fahrenheit 9/11, V931 (Box 19)
  - Hart InterCivic eSlate (English), V932 (Box 19)
  - Marcus Boon - NBC 6pm - 8pm, November 7, 2000; V933 (Box 19)
  - Marcus Boon - NBC 8pm - 10pm, November 7, 2000; V934 (Box 19)
  - Marcus Boon - NBC 10pm - 11pm, November 7, 2000; V935 (Box 19)
  - Marcus Boon - NBC 11pm - 1am, November 7-8, 2000; V936 (Box 19)
  - Marcus Boon - NBC 1am - 4am, November 8, 2000; V937 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Fighting Off Exhaustion, November 6, 2000; V938 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Presidential Election 2000, November 8, 2000; V939 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Focus on Palm Beach County, November 9, 2000; V940 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Town Meeting - Battle for the Ballot, November 10, 2000; V941 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Election Developments, November 13, 2000; V942 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Latest Developments in Florida, November 14, 2000; V943 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Battling in Florida, November 15, 2000; V944 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Voting Recount in Florida, November 16, 2000; V945 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Absentee Ballots, November 17, 2000; V946 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Making Their Case in Court, November 20, 2000; V947 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Florida Deadline, November 21, 2000; V948 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Developments in Florida, November 22, 2000; V949 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Answering the Call, November 23, 2000; V950 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: The Nation Waits, November 24, 2000; V951 (Box 19)
  - Nighline: A Visit To Capitol Hill, November 28, 2000; V952 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Media Blitz, November 29, 2000; V953 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Analysis of Today's Court Proceedings, December 1, 2000; V954 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Questions Yet to Be Answered, December 4, 2000; V955 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Today's Election Events, December 5, 2000; V956 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Minority Voters, December 6, 2000; V957 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: ABC 2000, The Nation Waits, December 7, 2000; V958 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: The Latest Decision, December 8, 2000; V959 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Supreme Court and the Latest on the Election, December 11, 2000; V960 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Supreme Court in Hearing, December 12, 2000; V961 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Is This the End, December 13, 2000; V962 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: Election Reform, December 14, 2000; V963 (Box 19)
  - Nightline: A Candidate Reflects, December 15, 2000; V964 (Box 19)
  - ABC News Program Listing, June 13, 2002 (Box 19)
  - ABC News Program Listing, December 4, 2002 (Box 19)
  - Florida Vote Recount Trial, Day 1, Part 1 of 4 (C-Span), December 2, 2000; V965 (Box 20)
  - Florida Vote Recount Trial, Day 1, Part 2 of 4 (C-Span), December 2, 2000; V966 (Box 20)
  - Florida Vote Recount Trial, Day 1, Part 3 of 4 (C-Span), December 2, 2000; V967 (Box 20)
  - Florida Vote Recount Trial, Day 1, Part 4 of 4 (C-Span), December 2, 2000; V968 (Box 20)
  - Florida Vote Recount Trial, Day 2, Part 1 of 8 (C-Span), December 3, 2000; V969 (Box 20)
  - Florida Vote Recount Trial, Day 2, Part 2 of 8 (C-Span), December 3, 2000; V970 (Box 20)
  - Florida Vote Recount Trial, Day 2, Part 3 of 8 (C-Span), December 3, 2000; V971 (Box 20)
  - Florida Vote Recount Trial, Day 2, Part 4 of 8 (C-Span), December 3, 2000; V972 (Box 20)
  - Florida Vote Recount Trial, Day 2, Part 5 of 8 (C-Span), December 3, 2000; V973 (Box 20)
  - Florida Vote Recount Trial, Day 2, Part 6 of 8 (C-Span), December 3, 2000; V974 (Box 20)
  - Florida Vote Recount Trial, Day 2, Part 7 of 8 (C-Span), December 3, 2000; V975 (Box 20)
  - Florida Vote Recount Trial, Day 2, Part 8 of 8 (C-Span), December 3, 2000; V976 (Box 20)
  - Volusia County Ballot Inspection Information, December 3, 2000; V977 (Box 20)
  - Mark Seibel, Miami Herald, December 19, 2001; TR8183a (Box 20)
  - MH - Kidwell/Tanfani on Votomatic Problems, TR8184a (Box 20)
  - Jon Freed Election Machine Service Co., January 22, 2002; TR8185a (Box 20)
  - Interview With Roy Saltman, February 19, 2002; TR8186a (Box 20)
  - Interview With Roy G. Saltman by Marcus Boon, April 1, 2002; TR8187a (Box 20)
  - Interview With Roy G. Saltman by Marcus Boon, April 1, 2002; TR8188a (Box 20)
  - Palm Beach Post: Interview With Reporters Joel Engelhardt and George Bennett, April 3, 2002; TR8189a (Box 20)
  - 3.5" Floppy Disk: Broward County General Election, Canvass Reports (Over and Under), November 7, 2000 (Box 20)
  - Voting Technology Archive Finding Aid, September 13, 2006 (Box 20)
  - Voting Technology Archive Finding Aid, September 13, 2006 (Box 20)
- Series VIII: Book Publications
  - Stealing Elections, 2004 (Box 26)
  - Chaotic Elections! A Mathematician Looks at Voting, 2001 (Box 26)
  - What Went Wrong in Ohio: The Conyers Report on the 2004 Presidential Election, 2005 (Box 26)
  - Election 2000: How the Military Vote Was Suppressed, 2001 (Box 26)
  - The Miami Harold Report: Democracy Held Hostage, 2001 (Box 26)
  - 36 Days: The Complete Chronicle of the 2000 Presidential Election Crisis, 2001 (Box 26)
  - Bush V Gore: The Court Cases and the Commentary, 2001 (Box 26)
  - The Accidental President, 2001 (Box 26)
  - Deadlock: The Inside Story of America's Closest Election, 2001 (Box 26)
  - The Unfinished Election of 2000: Leading Scholars Examine America's Strangest Election, 2001 (Box 26)
  - Supreme Injustice: How the Court Hijacked Election 2000, 2001 (Box 26)
  - What's the Matter With Kansas: How Conservatives Won the Heart of America, 2004 (Box 26)
  - The Votes That Counted: How the Court Decided the 2000 Presidential Election, 2001 (Box 26)
  - Black Box Voting: Ballot Tampering in the 21st Century, 2004 (Box 26)
  - Models of Voting in Presidential Elections, 2004 (Box 26)
  - Too Close To Call: The Thirty-Six-Day Battle To Decide the 2000 Election, 2001 (Box 26)
  - Steal This Vote: Dirty Elections and the Rotten History of Democracy in America, 2005 (Box 26)
  - Hanging Chads: The Inside Story of the 2000 Presidential Recount in Florida, 2004 (Box 26)
  - The Crisis of American Democracy: The Presidential Elections of 2000 and 2004 (Box 26)
  - If It's Not Close They Can't Cheat: Crushing the Democrats in Every Election and Why Your Life Depends On It., 2004 (Box 26)
  - Did George W. Bush Steal America's 2004 Election? Essential Documents, 2005 (Box 26)
- Series IX: Voting Technology Exhibit Items, October 28, 2004
  - Two Votamatic voting machines (Box 22)
    Miami-Dade County Florida butterfly ballot
  - Voting card punch mechanism (Box 23)
  - Voting Cards with hanging chads (Box 23)
  - Exhibit labels (Box 23)
  - Autographed photo reproduction of Theresa LePore, Carol Roberts, and Charles Burton counting hanging chads. (Box 23)
  - Certificate authenticating Palm Beach County voting machine signed by Theresa LePore (Box 23)
  - Styluses (Box 23)
  - Chads (Box 23)
  - Complete Palm Beach County voting machine
    Complete with silver case, butterfly ballot, light, legs, stylus, voting cards.
- Series X: Voting Technology Ephemera
  - Punch Cards (Box 24)
  - Styluses (Box 24)
  - Voting Punch Mechanisms (Box 24)
  - New T-strip, BRC Style (Box 24)
  - Notes Pertaining to Problems With Voting Machine (Box 24)
  - Judy Miller, Miami Herald City Editor, Note pads with notes (Box 24)